fourpxarticles.com 2010-11-03

# Privacy Policy | FourPx Articles

FourPx Articles is strongly committed to protecting your privacy while interacting with our content, products and services in a safe and secure environment.

**Collection of Information**

Information is collected from you primarily to make it easier and more rewarding for you to use our services. Depending on the service you are accessing, you could be asked to provide information such as your name, email address or information about what you like and do not like. It is entirely your choice whether to respond to these questions or not. FourPx Articles websites collects two types of information. They are,

  * Anonymous Information
  * Personal Information

**Anonymous Information**

We may collect information to tell us that five thousand people visit this Privacy Policy today, but we do not know their names, where they live or their date of birth – they are ‘anonymous’ to us. Another example of FourPx Articles website collecting anonymous information is when the FourPx Articles are invited to respond to surveys/polls on FourPx Articles website. The surveys/polls may ask you for demographic information such as your age, gender and postcode. This information is collected for research purposes, is used in the aggregate (where possible), and remains anonymous. Many of the individuals who access our services are anonymous to us.

**Personal Information**

The website will collect personal information that lets us know the specifics of who you are such as your name, email address, or postal address, when you provide it to us. With this information, FourPx Articles websites can provide a variety of personalized and enhanced services that are not available to anonymous users. We hope that you will find it beneficial to provide individually identifiable information about yourself to us because it will make our services more valuable to you.

Sometimes, we may specifically ask for personal information about you when you sign up to use a service. Certain information may be required, such as your name, age, internet address or screen name, billing address, type of computer, credit card number, in order to provide that service or product to you. This information may also be used to inform you of additional products and services which may interest you. You can choose not to receive such information when you are undertaking product or service registration on our website. We may also ask about your interests, but it is your choice whether to respond.

How much of your personal information that you choose to disclose to the FourPx Articles is completely up to you. The only way we know something about you personally is if you provide it to us, for example when you take part in a discussion forum or enter one of the competitions on our websites.

**Use of Anonymous Information**

FourPx websites automatically gathers anonymous information to monitor the use of FourPx websites like the numbers and frequency of visitors to FourPx websites and its areas, very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use such data in the aggregate. This collective data helps us determine how much our audiences use parts of the site, so we can improve FourPx websites to assure that they are as appealing as we can make it for as many users as possible. FourPx websites may publish or provide this aggregate data to other people.

**Use of Personal Information**

FourPx Articles website will only use the personal information you have chosen to provide us for the purpose for which you provided it. FourPx Articles website will not use it for any other purpose without your consent.

**Disclosure**

There will be occasions where it will be necessary for FourPx Articles to disclose your personal information to third parties. FourPx Articles may be required by law to disclose the information, or FourPx Articles may be required to disclose your personal information to third parties to provide the service you have requested, for example, if you purchase products online from the FourPx Articles website, FourPx Articles will need to disclose your personal information to third parties in order to bill and deliver your products. However, the disclosure will only be made where it is necessary to fulfill the purpose for which you disclosed your personal information. Otherwise than stated above, we do not disclose personal information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any organization or person outside FourPxArticles.com unless you have authorized us to do so. For example, when you contribute to an online forum you may want to publish your name and email address.

**No Sale of Personal Information**

Under no circumstances will FourPx Articles sell or receive payment for licensing or disclosing your personal information.

**Interacting with FourPx Articles**

There are many interactive features on FourPx Articles website that you can contribute to. These include: Article Submissions, Reviews, Comments, Online Subscriptions, Mailing Lists and Email.

When interacting with FourPx Articles website, we suggest that you use your discretion and exercise caution when providing your personal information.

Note that whenever you post personal information in publicly accessible places, such as chat rooms or message boards, this information becomes available to anyone with access to the Internet. This information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Therefore, we recommend that you refrain from posting any information that you do not want seen in these public areas.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any personal information. Be responsible whenever you are online.

**Access and correction: personal data**

If FourPx Articles holds your personal information, then FourPx Articles will where possible, provide you with access to the information. FourPx Articles will take reasonable steps to correct the information so that it is accurate, complete and up to date.

**Security**

FourPx Articles operates secure data networks that are designed to protect your privacy and security.

**Complaints About Privacy**

If you have any complaints relating to online privacy issues on our website, please notify FourPx Articles. While FourPx Articles accepts no liability for any material or links posted to the service, we will investigate all complaints.

**Changes to FourPx Articles Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change FourPx Articles Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here.
